homeworknow.com 2011-04-19

# What is the HomeworkNOW service privacy policy? : HomeworkNOW Help

**Policy Summary:**  The folks at HomeworkNOW.com believe that strong electronic privacy is crucial for the ongoing success of the Internet as a service, commercial, and entertainment medium. To this end, unless you designate otherwise, any information you enter on any HomeworkNOW.com related site or creation will remain strictly confidential. This means that we will not exchange your e-mail address, or any other personal information with anyone outside of HomeworkNOW.com. As with most sites, we collect general information on visits to our pages. This information is used only for statistical purposes. None of this information is linked back to you as an individual. Please see below for the specifics surrounding our Privacy Policy.

* * *

Privacy Policy for  **HomeworkNOW.com** , HomeworkNOW LLC company.

Our postal address is   
 **HomeworkNOW LLC  
6 Elton Ave  
Stratham, NH 03885**

We can be reached via the web at <http://www.homeworknow.com/contactus>   
or you can reach us by telephone, toll-free at in the US at 888.397.6297   
or from outside the US at +1.617.848.9488.

For each visitor to HomeworkNOW.com (our Web page), our Web servers automatically recognizes only the consumer's domain name and IP address.

**We collect only:**

  * the domain name and IP address, but not the e-mail address of visitors to our Web page,
  * aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit
  * information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations
  * no information on consumers who browse our Web page.

**The information we collect is:**

  * used for internal review and is then discarded, used to improve the content of our Web page
  * used to customize the content and/or layout of our page for each individual visitor
  * not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes.

**With respect to cookies:**  We use cookies to store visitor preferences and temporarily record session information, such as items that consumers add to their shopping cart.

**With respect to Ad Servers** : We do not partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies.

**With respect to customer information:**  From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will contact you before we use your data for these new purposes to notify you of the policy change and to provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses.

Upon request we provide site visitors with access to unique identifier information (e.g., customer number or password) that we maintain about them, transaction information (e.g., dates on which customers made purchases, amounts and types of purchases) that we maintain about them, communications that the consumer/visitor has directed to our site (e.g., e-mails, customer inquiries), and contact information (e.g., name, address, phone number) that we maintain about them . Consumers can access or correct this information by visiting us at [http://help.homeworknow.com](http://help.homeworknow.com/).

Although used as the primary source of communication between us and our customers, ff you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by contacting us at <http://www.homeworknow.com/contactus>.

If you supply us with your postal address on-line you will only receive the information for which you provided us your address.

Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line will only receive telephone contact from us with information regarding orders they have placed on-line with us, business development opportunities, or for technical support correspondence.

**With respect to security:**  When we transfer and receive certain types of sensitive information such as financial or health information, we redirect visitors to a secure server and will notify visitors through our site. We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site.

To help better protect our children, HomeworkNOW is rated and labeled with the ICRA and SafeSurf Internet Ratings Services, and complies fully with respect to federal privacy laws as they pertain to children and the Internet.

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above addresses or phone number.
